Suddenly a sound rings out, stopping you in your tracks.
一声铃响突然响起，让你停下手里的事。
Panicking, you search for where it could be coming from.
惊慌中，你寻找声音的来源。
It's your phone, and if you're like a quarter of 18 to 34-year-olds in a recent British study, you probably won't answer it.
是你的手机，如果你像最近一项英国研究中四分之一的18至34岁人群一样，你可能不会接听。
The same study found that 70% of people in this age group prefer text messages to phone calls.
同一研究发现，这个年龄段70%的人更喜欢发短信而不是打电话。
Why do so many people hate phone calls?
为什么这么多人讨厌打电话？
While previous generations grew up using landlines to talk to their friends, smartphone-equipped younger people have grown up accustomed to using text messages, group chats and voice notes for social conversations.
前几代人用固定电话与朋友聊天，而拥有智能手机的年轻人则习惯了用短信、群聊和语音留言进行社交对话。
What these media have in common is that they are asynchronous – they don't need to happen in real time.
这些媒体的共同点是它们是异步的——它们不需要实时发生。
When you can craft a reply free of interruption, you have greater control over your contributions to a conversation.
当你可以在不受干扰的情况下精心回复时，你就能更好地控制自己在对话中的发言。
It also means that you can reply when it's best for you.
这也意味着你可以在最适合自己的时候回复。
Synchronous communication, like phone calls or face-to-face conversations, can lead people to feel a loss of control and the corresponding anxiety.
同步通信，比如电话或面对面交谈，会让人感到失控并产生相应的焦虑。
Coupled to this is that fact that many young people report associating phone calls, particularly those without prior warning, with bad news.
与此相关的是，许多年轻人报告说，他们将电话（尤其是没有事先警告的电话）与坏消息联系在一起。
This means that new social codes are being established.
这意味着新的社交规范正在建立。
Many people will now text someone to see if they're available to take a phone call.
现在许多人会先发短信询问对方是否方便接电话。
If someone doesn't feel able to sum something up in a few short messages, they might leave a long voice note.
如果有人觉得无法用几条短信把事情说清楚，他们可能会留一条很长的语音留言。
Could it be that not wanting to intrude on someone with a sudden phone call is just a question of good manners and respecting someone's boundaries?
不想用突如其来的电话打扰别人，是否只是礼貌和尊重他人界限的问题？
Maybe, but this doesn't mean that anxiety around communication has been eliminated.
也许吧，但这并不意味着围绕沟通的焦虑已经消除。
Texting may be asynchronous, but many people report tensions from being 'left on read' – when you know someone has read your message, but they don't, or won't, reply.
短信可能是异步的，但许多人报告说，因"已读不回"而感到紧张——当你明知某人已读你的消息，但他们没有或不愿回复。
Many would agree with British writer Daisy Buchanan, who reminds us how picking up the phone to talk to someone can be far more effective at relieving tension than a series of awkward messages.
许多人会同意英国作家黛西·布坎南的观点，她提醒我们，拿起电话与人交谈在缓解紧张方面远比一连串尴尬的短信有效。
So, are these new social codes better at respecting boundaries, or are they just creating a whole new set of potential anxieties?
那么，这些新的社交规范是更好地尊重了界限，还是只是制造了一整套新的潜在焦虑？